Guide to the Consumer Reports. Advocacy records, 1927-2011 and undated RL.11780
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Statements, Comments, Testimonies, etc., 1954-2001 and undated; 3
  - 1974, 10
    - 7403019-1. Oil industry, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7403020-1. Economics, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7403021-1. Consumer complaints arbitration, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7403022-1. Balloons, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7403023-1. Bottles, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7403024-1. Balloons, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7403025-1. Balloons, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7403026-1. Nutritional labels, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7403027-1. Lead in milk products, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7403028-1. Aflatoxins in peanuts, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7403029-0. Baby cribs, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404001-1. Business, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404002-1. Natural gas, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404004-1. Meat pricing, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404005-1. Meat pricing, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404006-1. Cosmetics, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404007-1. Safety standards, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7404008-1. Credit cards, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404009-1. Credit cards, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404010-1. Credit cards, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404011-1. Credit cards, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404012-1. Credit cards, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404013-1. Credit cards, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404014-1. Credit cards, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404015-1. Credit cards, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404016-1. Credit cards, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404017-1. Lawyers, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7404018-1. Moving industry, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7404019-1. Moving industry, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7404020-1. Moving industry, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7404021-1. Pesticides, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404022-1. Public utilities, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404023-1. Lawyers, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404024-1. Data banks, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404025-1. Public utilities, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404026-1. Banks, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404027-1. Cable television, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404028-1. Dairy products, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404029-1. Food net weights, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404030-1. Nutritional labels, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404031-1. Soft drinks, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404032-1. Phosphates in ham, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404033-1. Detergent labeling, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404034-1. Business, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404035-1. Federal Trade Commission, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404036-1. Federal Trade Commission, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404037-1. Business, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7404038-1. Frozen food, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7405001-0. Steel imports, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7405002-1. Business, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7405003-1. Business, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7405004-1. Business, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7405005-1. Public utilities, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7405006-1. Adhesives, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7405007-1. Freedom of Information Act, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7405008-1. Diethylstilbestrol, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7405009-1. Periodical Correspondents Association, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7405010-1. Glass containers, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7405011-1. Credit cards, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7405012-1. Credit cards, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7405013-1. Credit cards, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7405014-1. Banks, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7405015-1. Oil industry, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7405016-1. Lead-based paint, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7405017-1. Standards, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7405018-1. Standards, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7405019-1. Child automobile restraints, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7405020-1. Bicycle child carriers, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7405021-1. Appliances, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7405022-1. Textile imports, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7405023-1. Meat definitions, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7405024-1. Children's clothing, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7405025-1. Children's clothing, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7405026-1. Children's clothing, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7405027-1. Children's clothing, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7405028-1. Food and Drug Administration, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7406001-1. Business, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7406002-1. Meat pricing, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7406003-1. Textile imports, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7406004-1. Textile care labels, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7406005-1. Gasoline, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7406006-1. Oil industry, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7406007-1. Enriched flour, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7406008-1. Savings bank life insurance, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7406009-1. Moving industry, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7406010-1. Carpet flammability, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7406011-1. Vitamins, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7406012-1. Radio, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7406013-1. Moving industry, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7406014-1. Carpet flammability, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7406015-1. Physicians' services, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7406016-1. Consumer complaints arbitration, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7406017-1. Children's clothing, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7406018-1. Children's clothing, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7406019-1. Food and Drug Administration, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7406020-1. Meat pricing, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7406021-1. Drug prices, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7406022-1. Life jackets, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7406023-1. Life jackets, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407001-1. Balloons, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407002-1. Balloons, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407003-1. Public utilities, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407004-1. Health care, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407005-1. Health care costs, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407006-1. Public utilities, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407007-1. Public utilities, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407008-1. Public utilities, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407009-1. Food supplements, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407010-1. Antitrust--Food, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407011-1. Meat grading and labeling, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407012-1. Tomatoes, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407013-1. Banks, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7407014-1. Beverages, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407016-1. Microwave ovens, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407017-1. Health care costs, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407018-1. Antitrust--Beverages, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407019-1. Beverages, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407020-1. Lawyers, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407021-1. Gasoline, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407022-1. Moving industry, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407023-1. Moving industry, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407024-1. Gasoline, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407025-1. Furniture flammability, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407026-1. Antitrust--Beverages, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407027-1. Hospitals, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407028-1. Tomatoes, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407029-1. Meat grading and labeling, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407030-1. Balloons, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407031-1. Children's clothing, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407032-1. Life jackets, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407033-1. Life jackets, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407034-1. Life jackets, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407035-1. Life jackets, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407036-1. Life jackets, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407037-1. Life jackets, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407038-1. Life jackets, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407039-1. Life jackets, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407040-1. Food supplements, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407041-1. Drug prices, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407042-0. Plastic, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7407043-1. Food supplements, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7408001-1. Beverages, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7408002-1. Cereals, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7408003-1. Cereals, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7408004-1. Cereals, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7408005-1. Food labeling, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7408006-1. Nutritional labels, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7408007-1. Beverages, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7408008-1. Food labeling, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7408009-1. Fish, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7408010-1. Food supplements, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7408011-0. Energy policy, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7408012-1. Drugs, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7408013-1. Trademarks, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7408014-1. Antitrust--Food, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7408015-1. Moving industry, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7408016-1. Lead-based paint, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7408017-1. Pesticides, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7408018-1. Pesticides, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7408019-1. Sweeteners, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7408020-1. Life jackets, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7408021-1. Life jackets, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7408022-1. Life jackets, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7408023-1. Life jackets, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7408024-1. Life jackets, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7408025-1. Cleaning products, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7409001-1. Toys, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7409002-1. Public utilities, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7409003-1. Public utilities, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7409004-1. Banks, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7409005-0. Television advertising to children, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7409006-1. Price-fixing, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7409007-1. Meat industry, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7409008-1. Television advertising to children, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7409009-1. Public utilities, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7409010-1. Periodical Correspondents Association, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7409011-1. Life insurance, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7409012-1. Lawyers, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7409013-1. Moving industry, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7409014-1. Lead-based paint, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7409015-1. Automobile fuel economy, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7409016-1. Banks, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7409017-1. Flammable fabrics, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7409018-1. Public utilities, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7409019-1. Automobile safety restraints, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7409020-1. Boat safety, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7409021-1. Sun lamps, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7409022-1. Business, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7409023-1. Tobacco, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7410001-1. Public utilities, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7410002-1. Public utilities, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7410003-1. Buses, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7410004-1. Natural gas, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7410005-1. Natural gas, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7410006-1. Food packaging, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7410007-1. Plastic, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7410008-1. Meat pricing, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7410010-1. Fats and oils labeling, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7410011-1. Food labeling, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7410012-1. Nutritional labels, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7410014-1. Credit cards, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7410015-1. Credit cards, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7410016-1. Lawyers, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7410017-1. Moving industry, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7410018-1. Lead-based paint, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7410019-1. Lead-based paint, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7410020-1. Prescription drugs, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7410021-1. Food standards, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7410022-1. Food labeling, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7410023-1. Life jackets, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7410024-1. Price-fixing, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7410025-1. Steel imports, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7411001-1. Automobile fuel economy, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7411002-1. Automobile fuel economy, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7411003-1. Regulatory agencies, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7411004-1. Freedom of Information Act, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7411005-1. Lead-based paint, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7411006-1. Natural gas, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7411007-1. Televisions, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7411008-1. Banks, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7411009-1. Gasoline, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7411010-1. Freedom of Information Act, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7411011-1. Food stamps, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7411012-1. Lawyers, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7411013-1. Lawyers, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7411014-1. Natural gas, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7411015-1. Moving industry, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7411016-1. Lead-based paint, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7411017-1. Lead-based paint, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7411018-1. Record keeping of consumer complaints, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7411019-1. Sampling plans, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7411020-1. Gasoline, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7411021-1. Meat grading and labeling, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7411022-1. Life jackets, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7411023-1. Business, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7411024-1. Fish, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412001-1. Frozen food, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412002-1. Food stamps, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412003-1. Food pricing, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7412004-1. Meat grading and labeling, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412005-1. Microwave ovens, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412006-1. Public utilities, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412007-1. Cereals, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412008-1. Food quality and safety, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412009-1. Gasoline, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7412010-1. Lawyers, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412011-1. Food advertising, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412012-1. Lawyers, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412013-1. Lead in milk products, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412014-1. Lead-based paint, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412015-1. Lead-based paint, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412016-1. Lead-based paint, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412017-1. Lead-based paint, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412018-1. Lead-based paint, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412019-1. Lead-based paint, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412020-1. Lead-based paint, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412021-1. Lead-based paint, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412022-1. Lead-based paint, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412023-1. Lead-based paint, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412024-1. Lead-based paint, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412025-1. Nutritional labels, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412026-1. Food stamps, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412027-1. Escrow accounts, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412028-1. Life jackets, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412029-1. Life jackets, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412030-1. Oil industry, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7412031-1. Food pricing, 1974 (Box 6)
  - 1975, 11
    - 7501001-1. Public utilities, 1975 (Box 6)
    - 7501002-1. Natural gas, 1975 (Box 6)
    - 7501003-1. Air transport, 1975 (Box 6)
    - 7501004-1. Freedom of Information Act, 1975 (Box 6)
    - 7501005-2. Activity report, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7501006-2. West Coast office, 1975 (Box 6)
    - 7501007-2. Drug advertising, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7501008-2. Drug advertising, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7501009-1. Food advertising, 1975 (Box 6)
    - 7501010-1. Food stamps, 1975 (Box 6)
    - 7501011-1. Food stamps, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7501012-1. Food stamps, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7501013-1. Food stamps, 1975 (Box 6)
    - 7501014-1. Food stamps, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7501015-1. Lawyers, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7501016-1. Alcoholic beverages, 1975 (Box 6)
    - 7501017-1. Food stamps, 1975 (Box 6)
    - 7501018-1. Air transport, 1975 (Box 6)
    - 7501019-1. Food industry, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7501020-1. Lead-based paint, 1975 (Box 6)
    - 7501021-1. Deodorants, 1975 (Box 6)
    - 7501022-1. Electricity supply, 1975 (Box 6)
    - 7501023-1. Deodorants, 1975 (Box 6)
    - 7501024-1. Medical malpractice, 1975 (Box 6)
    - 7502001-1. Natural gas, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7502002-1. Oil industry, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7502003-2. Prescription drugs, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7502004-2. Prescription drugs, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7502005-1. Lawyers, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7502008-1. Automobile insurance, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7502009-1. Appliances, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7502010-1. Prescription drugs, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7502011-1. Pets, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7502012-1. Pets, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7502013-1. Pets, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7502014-1. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7502015-1. Lawyers, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7502016-1. Lawyers, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7502017-1. Food industry, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7502018-1. Milk pricing, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7502019-1. Fruit, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7502020-1. Air transport, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7502021-1. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7502022-1. Council on Wage and Price Stability, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7502023-1. Television broadcasting, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7502024-1. Automobile brokers, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7502025-1. Food and Drug Administration, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7503001-1. Gasoline, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7503002-1. Life insurance, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7503003-0. Automobile fuel economy, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7503004-2. Prescription drugs, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7503005-1. Lawyers, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7503006-1. Food toxins, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7503007-1. Drained food weights, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7503008-1. Class actions, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7503009-1. Litigation, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7503010-1. Banks, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7503011-1. Council on Wage and Price Stability, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7503012-1. Public utilities, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7503013-1. Oil industry, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7503014-1. Banks, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7504001-1. Consumer fraud, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7504002-1. Beverages, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7504003-1. Beverages, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7504004-1. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7504005-1. Federal Reserve System, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7504006-1. Federal Energy Administration, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7504007-0. International trade, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7505001-1. Credit cards, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7505002-1. Televisions, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7505003-2. Health insurance, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7505004-2. Health insurance, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7505005-2. Licensing, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7505006-2. Licensing, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7505007-2. Licensing, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7505008-1. Banks, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7505009-1. Federal Trade Commission, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7505010-2. Prescription drugs, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7505011-2. Prescription drugs, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7505012-2. Food pricing, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7505013-2. Food pricing, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7505014-1. Natural gas, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7505015-1. Nutritional labels, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7505016-1. Oil industry, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7505017-1. Beverages, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7505018-1. Physicians' services, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7505019-1. Business, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7506001-2. Consumer protection, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7506002-1. Lead-based paint, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7506003-1. Federal Energy Administration, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7506004-1. Food quality and safety, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7506005-1. Antitrust, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7506006-1. Banks, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7506007-1. Regulatory agencies, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7506008-1. Equal Credit Opportunity Act, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7506009-1. Drained food weights, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7506010-1. Banks, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7506011-1. Conflict of interest, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7506012-1. Antitrust, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7506013-1. Drug advertising, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7506014-1. Automobile warranties, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7506015-1. Advertising, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7507001-1. Periodical Correspondents Association, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7507002-2. Price-fixing, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7507003-2. Milk, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7507004-2. Consumer protection, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7507005-2. Consumer protection, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7507006-2. Consumer protection, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7507007-1. Regulatory agencies, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7507008-1. Air transport, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7507009-1. Banks, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7507010-1. Consumer Leasing Act, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7507011-1. Consumer Leasing Act, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7507012-2. Prescription drugs, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7507013-1. Detergent labeling, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7507014-1. Credit Practices regulation, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7508001-2. Consumer protection, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7508002-2. Consumer protection, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7508003-2. Consumer protection, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7508004-2. Consumer protection, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7508005-1. Gasoline, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7508006-1. Lawyers, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7508007-1. Cosmetics, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7508008-1. Lead-based paint, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7508009-1. Television advertising to children, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7509001-1. Cosmetics, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7509002-1. Product hazards, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7509003-1. Food advertising, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7509004-1. Lawyers, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7509005-1. Lawyers, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7509006-1. Credit, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7510001-2. Prescription drugs, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7510002-2. Prescription drugs, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7510003-2. Consumer protection, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7510004-2. Consumer protection, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7510005-2. Licensing, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7510006-2. Licensing, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7510007-1. Food and Drug Administration, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7510008-1. Medical devices, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7510009-1. Funerals, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7510010-0. Steel imports, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7510011-2. Food pricing, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7510012-1. Natural gas, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7510013-1. Banks, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7510014-2. Lawyers, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7510015-2. Lawyers, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7511001-1. Life insurance, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7511002-0. Product testing, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7511003-1. Air conditioners, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7511004-1. Eye care, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7512001-2. Consumers Union, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7512002-1. Food and Drug Administration, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7512003-1. Footwear, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7512004-1. Air transport, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7512005-1. Air transport, 1975 (Box 16)
    - 7512006-1. Natural gas, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7512007-1. Air transport, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7512008-1. Garnishment, 1975 (Box 7)
    - 7512009-1. Antacids, 1975 (Box 7)
  - 1976, 12
    - 7601001-1. Food advertising, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7601002-1. Cosmetics, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7601003-1. Natural gas, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7601004-1. Consumer participation, 1976 (Box 16)
    - 7601005-1. Food advertising, 1976 (Box 16)
    - 7601006-1. Garnishment, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7601007-1. Blood products, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7602001-1. Periodical Correspondents Association, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7602002-1. Textile imports, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7602003-1. Banks, 1976 (Box 16)
    - 7602004-1. Air transport, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7602005-1. Food advertising, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7602006-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 16)
    - 7602007-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 16)
    - 7602008-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 16)
    - 7602009-1. Natural gas, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7602010-1. Natural gas, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7602011-2. Drained food weights, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7602012-1. Food industry, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7602013-1. Hearing aids, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7602014-1. Food grading, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7602015-1. Garnishment, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7602016-1. Garnishment, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7602017-1. Prescription drugs, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7602018-1. Cosmetics, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7602019-0. Lawn mowers, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7602020-1. Nutritional advertising, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7602021-2. Dairy products, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7602022-1. Air transport, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7602023-1. Consumer participation, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7602024-1. Funerals, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7602025-1. Nutritional advertising, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7603001-1. Life insurance, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7603002-1. Life insurance, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7603003-1. Life insurance, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7603004-2. Dairy products, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7603005-1. Banks, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7603006-1. Televisions, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7603007-1. Televisions, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7603008-1. Air transport, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7603009-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7603010-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7603011-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7603012-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7603013-1. Eye care, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7603014-1. Cosmetics, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7603015-1. Dairy products, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7603016-2. Dairy products, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7603017-2. Dairy products, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7603018-2. Dairy products, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7603019-2. Dairy products, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7603020-2. Dairy products, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7603021-2. Dairy products, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7603022-1. Eye care, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7603023-0. Prescription drugs, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7603024-1. Banks, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7603025-1. Banks, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7604001-1. Public utilities, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7604002-1. Public utilities, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7604003-1. Life insurance, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7604004-1. Life insurance, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7604005-1. Food advertising, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7604006-1. Footwear, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7604007-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7604008-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7604009-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7604010-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7604011-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7604012-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7604013-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7604014-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7604015-1. Credit, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7604016-1. Drug advertising, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7604017-1. Textile imports, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7604018-1. Antacids, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7604019-1. Funerals, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7604020-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7604021-1. Credit, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7604022-2. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7604023-1. Banks, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7605001-1. Life insurance, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7605002-1. Life insurance, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7605003-2. Dairy products, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7605004-1. Eye care, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7605005-1. Banks, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7605006-1. Life insurance, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7605008-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7605009-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7605010-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7605011-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 17)